This is today's target!
今回のターゲットはこちら
Homicidal NEXT, Kaburagi T. Kotetsu.
殺人犯ＮＥＸＴ
鏑木・Ｔ・虎徹
He is suspected of killing 68-year-old Samantha Taylor,
シュテルンビルド在住の
サマンサ・テイラーさんを
a resident of Stern Bild.
殺害した容疑がかけられています
Which Hero is going to arrest this vicious criminal?
さあ
この凶悪犯を逮捕するのは…
Dad...
お父さん
どのヒーローだ
What's going on?
どういうことだ
Damn! Is it broken?
だあ 壊れてんのか ああっ
At a time like this?
こんな時に
Hey, wait...
あっおおい ちょっと
You've got the wrong idea. I'm not who you think!
あっいやいや 違うんだって
おれは怪しいもんじゃ
It's the murderer!
殺人犯だあ！
キャー
Hello?
おーい
Damn!
だあ
All personal data regarding
鏑木虎徹とヒーローＴＶ関係者を
結びつけるパーソナルデータを
Kaburagi Kotetsu's association with HERO TV personnel
have been deleted from the network server, sir.
ネットワーク上からすべて
デリートいたしました
Good work.
ご苦労さま
yabureta PAGE wa ubawaretanda yo
That torn page was stolen,
破れたページは
奪われたんだよ
dokoka de otoshita oboe wa nai kara
since I don't remember ever dropping it anywhere.
何処かで落とした
覚えはないから
iwakan mo nai hodo kirei ni nai soko ni wa
In the place where the page used to be,
違和感もないほど
綺麗にないそこには
yume to iu nano shou ga tashikani atta
there was a chapter entitled "Dreams."
夢という名の章が確かにあった
nani wo nikumeba ii? kako ka jibun jishin ka
But who should I blame? The past? Myself?
何を憎めばいい？
過去か自分自身か
dekireba hoka no dareka de are
If possible, I hope it's someone else.
出来れば他の誰かであれ
monogatari no bokura ga sono mirai wo omou no wa
We, the characters in the story, think of the future.
物語の僕らが
その未来想うのは
nakushita ato demo shuyaku wa kawarenai kara
Because even after we're gone, the main character can't change.
失くした後でも
主役は変われないから
shousan nante sarenakutatte tashikana kyou ga aru nara
Even if I'm not praised, as long as today is here,
賞賛なんてされなくたって
確かな今日があるなら
yume nante namae no shou wa ikura demo tsukurerunda
I can make as many chapters as I want entitled "Dreams."
夢なんて名前の章は
いくらでも創れるんだ
The police have yet to find any information
What's the deal here, Ms. Agnes?!
おい アニエスさんよ
これ いったいどうなってるんだ
on Kaburagi T. Kotetsu, the suspect in this murder.
どちら様？
Who is this?
俺だよ 俺
It's me, Kotetsu!
虎徹だよ
Kotetsu? Kaburagi Kotetsu?!
虎徹？
鏑木虎徹？
ああ
Is this some sort of special event for HERO TV?!
これヒーローＴＶのイベントか何かか？
俺 何にも聞いてねえぞ
Nobody told me anything about this!
Are you really Kaburagi Kotetsu?
あなた本当に鏑木虎徹なの？
いやっ 当たり前だろ
Of course I am! I'm near the studio right now.
今 局の近くにいんだけど
What should I do?
どうしたらいんだ 俺
Kaburagi Kotetsu is near the studio!
鏑木虎徹がＯＢＣ付近にいるわ
Get everyone on the scene right away!
みんなすぐ 現場へゴー
へ？
Huh?
わざわざ宣戦布告してくるなんて
いい度胸ね
You've got some guts challenging us like this.
Do you really think you'll be able to get away that easy?
逃げ切る自信があるってことかしら
Huh? What are you talking about, Ag—
はあ？　何言ってんだよ
わああ あっ
Kaburagi Kotetsu, suspected murderer of Samantha Taylor!
サマンサ・テイラー殺しの犯人
鏑木虎徹
えっ
Huh?
Oh...
あっ
君はすでに包囲されている
おとなしく投降したまえ
You're surrounded. Quietly turn yourself in!
Quit showing off! I didn't do anything!
なーに かっこつけてんだよ
俺 何にもやってねえって
That is not for me to judge.
それは私の知る所ではない
The courts will decide whether you're innocent or not!
身の潔白は司法の手に
委ねるといい
たあっ とおー
I shall capture you!
You never listen, do you?!
相変わらず人の話を聞かねえ奴だな
えいっ はっ
Sky... High! And High!
スカーイ ハイッハッハーイ
あっ どわっ
どわっ たたたっ たあ
ぶわー
うおっ
Huh? Hey!
でえっ ちょちょっ だっだあ
What the hell is going on?
何がどうなってやがんだ？
The number you have reached is no longer in service.
お客様のおかけになった電話番号は
現在使われておりません
Please check—
番号を…
ふー
きっと あの事件は何かの間違いだから
その…
Don't worry, I'm sure this is all just a misunderstanding.
わかってるよ　おばあちゃん
I know, Grandma.
Kaede...
楓
I know Dad wouldn't do something that bad.
だってお父さんが
そんな悪いことするなんて思えないよ
He's a liar and he's silly, but Dad would never kill anyone!
嘘つきでかっこ悪いけど
お父さんは絶対 人殺しなんかしない
Never!
絶対！
あっ
うん
Yes.
あ…
Actually, Kaede.
実はね 楓
お父さんの本当の仕事はね
Your father's real job is being a Hero.
ヒーローなの
What?
えっ
He wasn't able to be by your side
楓のそばにいてやれなかったのはね
because he's been keeping the peace in the city as a Hero.
ヒーローとしてずっと
街の人たちの平和を守っていたからなの
I'm sorry for not telling you.
ごめんね ずっと黙ってて
You're kidding...
嘘…
I'm not kidding.
嘘なんかじゃないわ 楓
ワイルドタイガーって知ってるでしょ
You know of Wild Tiger, don't you, Kaede?
あの人が あなたのお父さんなの
He's your father.
はっ
There was a call from the fugitive, Kaburagi Kotetsu.
逃亡中の鏑木虎徹から
コンタクトがあったそうだ
奴はまだ市内に潜伏している
He's still hiding within the city.
Set up checkpoints everywhere you can!
各所に検問を実施するよう 要請を
Isn't there any information on Kaburagi Kotetsu?
鏑木虎徹に関する情報は
他にないのか
今のところ
Aside from the fact that he's a NEXT,
ＮＥＸＴであるということ以外
詳しい事情は つかめておりません
we haven't been able to find anything on him.
えっ
いー
I should have known.
そりゃそうだな
はいっ はいっ はいっ
はーい はいっ
Well, someone sure looks all pumped and ready.
やる気満々じゃねえかよ
わあー
There's nowhere to run!
もう逃げ場はないでござる
いやっ折紙
Origami!
So you finally showed up!
やっと現れたね
たあっ
Wait.
ちょっ
Now then.
さあ 神妙にお縄を頂戴するでござるよ
Come quietly!
I said wait!
おいっ待てって　ヒーローの俺が
殺しなんてする訳ないだろ
A Hero like me would never kill someone!
This is some kind of mistake!
これは何かの間違いなんだって
This criminal has got some nerve calling himself a Hero.
自分をヒーローだなんて
随分 図々しいこと言うね
この犯人
Huh?
はあ
What?
Wait a second, it's me!
いやいや 俺だよ俺
Take a good look!
よく見ろって
Kaburagi Kotetsu...
鏑木虎徹
That's right!
そう
よしっ逮捕
You're under arrest!
Explain to me what's going on!
だーかーらー
どうしてそうなんだよ
Can't you tell who I am?
お前ら俺のことわかんね…
There's nothing to explain!
どうもこうも
ねえだろ
にっ いー
てめえみたいな悪党を捕まえ
ポイントを稼ぐのが
Earning points by capturing crooks like you is our job!
俺等の仕事なんだよ
You idiot! I'm your best friend.
お前 親友の俺に…
Best friend?
親友だと？
What kind of nonsense is that, you low life!
何なめたこと言ってんだ？
外道の分際で
What?!
何だと
Okay, that's it...
いい加減にしろよ
この野郎
You bastard!
ぬおっ
This guy...
こいつ パワー系のＮＥＸＴか
He's a power-type NEXT!
Come back here!
待て
ええ
The murderer showed up at his home,
自宅前に現れた殺人犯が
再び 行方をくらました模様です
but he has disappeared once again!
Also, the suspect Kaburagi T. Kotetsu
なお 犯人 鏑木・Ｔ・虎徹の能力は
パワー系であるという情報が入っ…
is reported to be a power-type NEXT.
How do you feel?
気分はどうかね？
おっ
Sorry for all the trouble, sir.
ご心配をおかけして すみませんでした
僕はもう大丈夫です
I'm fine now.
I'll head out to make the arrest right now.
すぐに奴の逮捕に向かいます
そうか ちょうど良かった
I see. This is perfect.
うん？
A new version of the Hero suit was in development,
やあ ニューバージョンのスーツ開発が
佳境だったんだが
君のも完成したという連絡が入ってね
and I've just received word that yours was completed.
For me?
僕のも
ああ
Yes. A new suit for both you and Tiger.
君とタイガー揃ってリニューアルだ
Now the stage is set.
これでようやく役者が揃った
あっ痛ってえ
That hurt.
That cow is hard as a rock.
固過ぎなんだよ あの石
Huh?
あっ ううー
This one's gonna be a pain in the neck.
来たか 面倒くせえのが
Damn it! I'm not some sewer rat.
だあっ ドブネズミじゃねえんだ 俺は
I'm Wild Tiger!
ワイルドタイガーだぞ
Dad is...
お父さんが…
Wild Tiger...
ワイルドタイガー
Yeah, I'm not worried.
ああ 心配はしてない
I know it's all just some misunderstanding, Mom.
何かの間違いなのはわかってるよ
母さん
Anyway, how's Kaede?
それより楓の様子はどうだ
She's taking it quite well.
意外と落ち着いてるわ
It seems she's more mature than we thought.
あの子 私たちが思ってる以上に
大人だったみたい
I see. That's good.
そうか 良かった
Kaede?
楓
えー へっへっ
You don't give up, do you?
往生際の悪い男ね
Do you think you can just run away from me?
私から逃げられると思ってるの？
I'm not running away because I want to, you know?!
俺だって
逃げたくて 逃げてる訳じゃ
ねえんだよ　どおっ
See? I told you.
ほらね
もう逃げられないわよ
There's nowhere for you to run.
You murderer.
殺人犯
I told you, I didn't kill anyone!
だから俺は
殺しなんて してねんだって
How many times do I have to say this?!
何回 言やあ わかるんだよ
There's proof.
証拠は あがってるの
いい加減 罪を認めた方が賢明よ
It would be best if you admitted to your crimes,
鏑木虎徹
Kaburagi Kotetsu.
What happened to you guys? Why don't you recognize me?
なあ 一体 何があったんだ？
どうして俺が わかんねえんだよ
ん？
Come on, it's me!
よく見ろって
俺だよ 俺
Remember that time when you weren't sure about your career?
覚えてんだろ
お前が悩んでる時なんか
バーでチップやったじゃないか
How I gave you a tip at the bar
because I thought your singing was good?
歌 上手いなってさ
何言ってんの？
What are you talking about?
ええっ
What?
あれはワイルドタイガーにもらったのよ
Wild Tiger was the one who tipped me.
How do you know about my private life?!
何であんたが
そんなプライベート知ってるのよ
だから俺がその
ワイルドタイガーだからだろが
That's because I'm Wild Tiger!
冗談 言わないでよ
Stop joking around.
えっ
Nobody knows Wild Tiger's true identity.
確かにワイルドタイガーの正体は
誰にも明かされてない
You have some nerve to make such claims
顔も名前もわからないからって
よくもそんな図々しこと言えるわね
just because we don't know his real face or name.
おーい ちょっと待てって
どういうこ…
Hey, wait a second. What do you mean?
動かないで
Freeze!
それ以上 訳のわからないこと言うと
容赦しないわよ
I'll show no mercy if you insist on talking such nonsense.
You're the one who's talking nonsense!
訳わかんないこと言ってるのは
どっちだよ
おっ
Did you even forget about the time I gave you that towel too?
なあ 俺がタオルあげたことも
忘れちまったのか
Remember? I spilled coffee on your towel and ruined it.
思い出せよ
ほらっ
俺がコーヒーこぼして
お前のタオル駄目にしちまって
And I gave you a really cool towel to replace it.
その代りに 素敵なタオルあげただろ
えっ
I really am Wild Tiger!
本当に俺がワイルドタイガーなんだって
信じてくれよ
Please believe me!
Did you remember?
思い出したか
うおっ
えっ だあっ
Damn! Who is it this time?!
今度は誰だ？
Wild...
ワイルド…
...Tiger?
タイガー？
Ah, looks like we're finally back on air.
おっ ようやく中継が繋がりました
と いきなりワイルドタイガー
And there's Wild Tiger making a wild entrance in his new suit!
ニュースーツでワイルドに登場だ
Is the suspect finally going to be arrested?!
遂に 犯人逮捕となるか
You've got to be kidding me.
ふざけんじゃねえ
I'm Wild Tiger!
ワイルドタイガーは俺だよ
誰だ お前？
So who are you?!
おっ えっ
おっ
ふっ
ええっ
どわっ
おー
おりゃあ
ふー
Are you serious?
マジで？
Guess I have no choice.
仕方ねえなあ
See ya!
さいなら！
どわっ
どわあっ うっ
だへっ
だーへっ
Who the hell are you?
一体何もんだ おい
And what's with that suit?!
何なんだよ そのスーツ
Aww, you already found him?!
あーん もう見つけちゃってたの
You always steal the show, Lil' Tiger.
ホント おいしいとこ持ってくんだから
タイガーちゃんは
Hey... Who are you talking to?
おーい 誰としゃべってんだよ
お前
Who am I talking to? Don't you know who Wild Tiger is?
いや 誰って
ワイルドタイガーも知らないの あーた
いやあ だって 俺が
But I'm Wild Tiger!
自分がワイルドタイガーだなんて
嘘じゃない
You lied about being Wild Tiger.
ええっ
Hey, what happened to you guys?
なあ どうしたんだよ
お前ら
俺たち
Aren't we friends who have fought alongside each other?
ずっと一緒に
戦ってきた
仲間じゃねえか
Have you really forgotten who I am?
ホントに俺のこと…
忘れちまったのかよ
何言ってんのかしら
気味の悪い男
What is this creepy old man talking about?
早く連行しちゃいなさい
Hurry up and take him away.
ぬえっ ぬぇ
これが貴様の最後なのか
Is this how it's going to end for you?
What?
えっ
Lunatic?!
ルナティック？
Wait! Wait a second!
だああ えー ちょっと待て
I'm not the murderer.
俺は犯人じゃ
Reflect carefully upon your actions.
刮目して己のすべてを顧みよ
Why are you helping me?
どうしてお前
Passing judgment on those who are truly sinful
真の罪人を裁きのしるべに
導くことこそ私の正義
is my idea of justice.
翻って 今 貴様が偽りの正義の手に
委ねられること
Therefore, allowing you to be captured
by the hands of false justice goes against my beliefs.
それを看過するのは私の信条に反する
Say what?
はあ？
鏑木虎徹
Kaburagi Kotetsu.
Is this how you're going to let your idea of justice end?
貴様の正義とは
こんな所で潰えてしまうものなのか
えっ
What do you think you're doing?!
ちょっと どういうつもりよ
You plan on defending that murderer?!
あんた殺人犯をかばう気
No.
いいな 私はタナトスの声に
I only obey the voice of Thanatos.
従うまで
事件の容疑者 鏑木・Ｔ・虎徹は…
Kaburagi T. Kotetsu, the suspect in this case, is still on the run.
Why did Lunatic help me?
ルナティックの奴
どうして俺のことを…
The Heroes are continuing to track him down.
Hey...
なあ
ここは俺の縄張りだから
よそへ行ってくんねえか 新入り
This is my spot.
It looks like we've got some breaking news on this story.
Could you go somewhere else, new guy?
I'm not a new guy.
“新入り”じゃねえよ
I don't care.
何でもいいけどよ
ここに居られちゃ
商売の邪魔なんだよ
You're ruining business by staying here.
Come on, out, out!
ほれ 行った行った
We have a scoop!
スクープです
Our camera has caught No. 1 Hero Mr. Barnaby Brooks Jr.,
静養中との情報があったトップヒーロー
バーナビー・ブルックスJr.さんの姿を
who was reported to be resting away from home!
我々のカメラが捕らえました
えっ！
What?!
Bunny!
バニー
He's safe.
無事だったのか
During his time away, Barnaby is said to have been staying
なお バーナビーさんは
姿を見せなくなっていた期間
アルバート・マーベリック氏の別荘に
身を寄せていた模様です
at Mr. Albert Maverick's vacation house.
Huh?
えっ
Please, rest assured, the criminal terrorizing this city will be
ご安心ください
世間を にぎわせている犯人は
必ずや復讐に燃えるバーナビーが
捕まえて見せるでしょう
brought to justice by Barnaby, who is thirsting for vengeance.
The victim, Ms. Samantha Taylor,
なぜなら
被害者のサマンサ・テイラーさんこそ
身寄りのない彼の “家族”と呼べる
数少ない人物だからです
was one of the few people he could call family.
スクープだ！
It's a scoop!
Dig up information on the victim right away!
Mr. Maverick was with Bunny all this time?
マーベリックさんが ずっとバニーと…
I thought that you might know what had happened to him.
君なら知っているかと思ったんだが
Ms. Samantha has a photograph she wants to show you.
サマンサさんが
君に見せたい写真があるそうだ
This is...
これは…
Reﬂect carefully upon your actions.
己のすべてを顧みよ
I get it now.
そういうことか
あれっお前
Huh? Aren't you?
なっ
うっ
えっ
どわあーっ
ベンさん お願い
Ben! It's me!
Get in.
乗れ
Thank goodness.
あー良かった
You still remembered me.
あんたは覚えててくれたか
There's no one else I can rely on anymore.
もう他に頼れる人もいなくて
I figured you would pass by eventually if I stayed there.
あそこにいりゃあ
いつか通ると思ってたんすよ
Where are you going?
どこ… 行くんすか
えー ベンさん
まさかあんたまで俺を忘れちまったのか
Ben? Don't tell me you forgot who I am too?
Shut up and stay put.
黙って乗ってろ
Hey... Don't take me to the police.
おーい 警察は勘弁してくれよ
本当に俺 何にもしてねえんだ
I really didn't do anything!
Please! Stop the car!
頼む 止めてくれって
Believe me, Ben!
信じてくれよ ベンさん
どあっ
Calm down, Kotetsu.
落ち着け 虎徹
And you call yourself a Hero?
お前それでもヒーローか
うえっ
I don't know what happened to you,
何があったか知らねえけど
but we're pals who fought alongside each other for years.
俺たちゃ ずっと一緒に戦ってきた
仲間じゃねえか
You like this even if they're cold, right?
冷めてんのも好きだったろ お前
うん
はふっ
Jeez.
ったく 腹空かせてんじゃねえかと
思って 探してみりゃあよ
I figured you might be hungry, so I was looking for you.
And you think I've forgotten you?
俺がお前のこと
忘れる訳ねえじゃねえか
Sorry.
すんません
I won't forget you, no matter what! After all, I am your fan!
何があったって忘れねえ
俺はお前のファンだからな
んっ
Hey, is this?!
これって
Yeah. Brings back memories, doesn't it?
ああ 懐かしいだろ
This suit is filled with the memories of
俺とお前の思い出が詰まったスーツだ
the good old times we spent together.
I always keep it with me.
いつも肌身離さず持ってるんだぞ
Ben!
ベンさん
えっ
Hey, it's all wrinkled.
あのっ これ しわくちゃなんですけど
うっ えー
Don't worry about little things like that.
細けえことは気にすんな
てっ
へっ へっ
くふふっ
はははっ
ははははっ
へへっ へへっ へっ
Anyway, I'm surprised, Kotetsu.
でも驚いたぜ 虎徹
When I turned on the TV,
テレビつけたら いきなりお前が
殺人犯扱いでよ
they were treating you as if you were a murderer!
I've been framed.
はめられたんすよ 俺
This is where Dad works?
ここがお父さんの
Sorry, Grandma.
ごめんね おばあちゃん
Young lady, are you lost?
お嬢ちゃん 迷子にでもなったのかい？
いえ あの…
No, umm...
I want to meet Barnaby!
私 バーナビーに会いたいんです
Barnaby?
バーナビーに？
Yeah.
うん バーナビーならきっと
I figured that Barnaby might help me out.
私の力になってくれると…
I see.
そうか
お嬢ちゃんは
バーナビーのファンなんだね
You're one of Barnaby's fans, aren't you?
Thank you.
ありがとう
Unfortunately, he's busy.
しかし彼は忙しくてね
He can't help you with your request at the moment.
今はお願いを聞いてあげることが
できないんだ
Sorry.
ごめんよ
I see.
なるほどな
This is all Maverick's doing, huh?
すべてはマーベリックの
仕業って訳か
It certainly makes sense.
確かに筋は通るな
He even went through the trouble of
ご丁寧に 俺のニセもんまで
用意してくれやがって
getting someone to pretend to be me.
Who is that guy?
誰なんだよ あいつ
Wow. You've made enemies with the wrong guy.
まったく 厄介な奴を敵に回したもんだ
お前は
そういう役回りなんすよ 昔っから
It always happens to me.
だけど そうなると気がかりなのは
バーナビーだな
But if that's the case, I'm concerned about Barnaby.
Yeah.
ええ きっと あいつも他の奴らと
同じように
I'm sure that he doesn't remember me at all
俺のことなんかこれっぽちも
覚えちゃいないでしょうね
just like everyone else.
Are you saying that
忘れちまってるのも
マーベリックの仕業だってのか
Maverick is the reason why they've forgotten about you?
Who knows?
さあ 本人なのか 他のＮＥＸＴか
I don't know if it's his doing or some other NEXT.
In any case, a NEXT power is definitely the cause of this.
どっちにしても 何らかの
能力であることは間違いないでしょうね
So what now?
どうすんだ これから
For now, I'm going to try to make them
とりあえず 俺が本物の
ワイルドタイガーっだってことを
remember that I'm the real Wild Tiger.
思い出させてやりますよ
But how?
どうやって
I have a plan.
秘策があるんですよ
A plan?
秘策
I wouldn't be able to do this without you, Ben.
あなたのお蔭です
ベンさん
うん？
What's wrong?
どうしたの？
Well...
いえねえ
アポロンメディアの屋上に
鏑木虎徹らしき男が現れたんですが
A man who resembles Kaburagi Kotetsu
is on the roof of Apollon Media.
“らしき男”？
A man who resembles him?
ええ そいつが
自分が本物のワイルドタイガーだから
Yes.
He says he's the real Wild Tiger
and he wants us to call over all of the Heroes.
“ヒーロー全員を呼べ”とか言いだして
はあ？　どういうこと
What does that mean?
ん
What is this?
何よこれ
Looks like most of you are here.
全員揃ったみたいだな
All right, it's time to let out...
じゃ ワイルドに
...a Wild Roar!
吠えるか
灰色に染まる街の片隅で
hai iro ni somaru machi no katasumi de souzou dake no yume wo miteita
In an obscure corner of the ashen city, I was having a surreal dream.
想像だけの夢をみていた
存在する事の意味を
sonzai suru koto no imi wo nantonaku kangaehajimeta
I started to think about the meaning of existence.
なんとなく考え始めた
But I never know
BUT, I NEVER KNOW.
But, I never know.
myself＆夢＆
MYSELF AND yume AND TRUE AND ANYMORE
Myself & dreams & truth & anymore.
true＆Anymore
もう… もっと…
mou... motto...
At all...
こんな世界で私に聞いたの
konna sekai de watashi ni kita no ittai nani ga dekiru no ka wo
I asked myself what one can do in a world like this.
一体何が出来るのかを
あなたの笑顔が教えてくれたような
anata no egao ga oshiete kureta youna sonna kigashita kara
And I felt that your smiling face could teach me the answer.
そんな気がしたから
光を見つけたような
hikari wo mitsuketa youna itami ni furerareru
And enabled me to be touched by the pain of finding light.
痛みに触れられる
そう そんな気がした
sou, sonna kigashita
Yes, that was the feeling.
人は皆儚い夢を
hito wa mina hakanai yume wo kono te ni ireru tame ni
In pursuing their fleeting dreams,
この手に入れる為に
永遠の真実さえ見失う
eien no shinjitsu sae miushinau
people lose sight of the eternal truth.
消えない悲しい明日に
kienai kanashii asu ni hikari wo kureta no wa daredemo naku tatta hitori
No one made me realize that there is a light that never dims but you,
光をくれたのは
誰でもなく たった一人
過去も未来も分かち合えるずっと
shinjitai
I want to believe.
kako mo mirai mo wakachiaeru zutto
always sharing the past and the future.
えー　なーに
What is that?
あっ
お父さん
Dad?
こいつ 何をするつもりだ
What is he planning to do?
ども TIGER ＆ BUNNYの
新聞は広告から目を通すほう
虎徹です
Hi! I'm Kotetsu, the member of Tiger & Bunny
who looks through the ads first when he reads the newspaper!
よっしゃあ！
みんな まとめて かかってこい
All right! Come at me all at once!
楓 どうしてお前
やめろー
Kaede?! Why are you here?
次回　TIGER ＆ BUNNY
No!
バッド ラック オッフ… だっ
Next time on Tiger & Bunny:
Damn!